[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In Arsenic and Old Lace, what tune is Elaine whistling for Mortimer to come and get her?", "correct_answer": "Here Comes the Bride", "incorrect_answers": ["Happy Birthday", "Hi, Ho, Hi, Ho, its off to work we go", "Sixteen Tons"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "How many pleats are on a traditional Chefs hat (the Grand Toque)?", "correct_answer": "100", "incorrect_answers": ["70", "50", "20"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Where is Madagascar?", "correct_answer": "Off the Southeast Coast of Africa", "incorrect_answers": ["Off the Southeast Coast of South America", "Off the Southeast Coast of South America", "Off the Southwest Coast of Africa"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What continent did tomatoes originate from?", "correct_answer": "South America", "incorrect_answers": ["Asia", "North America", "Europe"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the literal meaning of the Latin phrase per fumum from which the modern word perfume originated?", "correct_answer": "Through smoke", "incorrect_answers": ["Under a veil", "Inside a haze", "Through fire"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the mathematical term for the shape of a footballs path, when thrown form one player to another?", "correct_answer": "Parabola", "incorrect_answers": ["Catenary", "Hyperbola", "Ellipse"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Sylvester Stallones other major success was First Blood,where he played the troubled Vietnam war veteran John Rambo. The movie was released in this year.", "correct_answer": "1982", "incorrect_answers": ["1990", "1981", "1985"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these statements about Petroleum, sometimes called \u2018black gold\u2019, is not true?", "correct_answer": "It is a renewable resource.", "incorrect_answers": ["It is used for the production of solvents, fertilizers and plastics.", "It is found in formations in he Earth.", "It is a fossil fuel."]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The team of this country won the first FIFA Womens World Cup.", "correct_answer": "The USA", "incorrect_answers": ["Italy", "Brazil", "Germany"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the main food source for the sloth, an omnivorous mammal living in Central and South America?", "correct_answer": "Leaves", "incorrect_answers": ["Small reptiles", "Insects", "Fruit"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The oldest known aromatherapy text describes a medical practice which relied on aromatics. It is from the Sumerian period and approximately this old.", "correct_answer": "3500 BC", "incorrect_answers": ["2000 BC", "2500 BC", "1000 BC"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is a cappuccino?", "correct_answer": "Espresso plus aerated milk", "incorrect_answers": ["Coffee plus aerated milk", "Coffee plus aerated milk plus chocolate", "Espresso plus aerated milk plus chocolate"]}]